There's a new pack in town
Z-O-M-B-I-E-S 2 is a fantasy, romance, tv movie film directed by Paul Hoen.
Zed and Addison are back at Seabrook High, where, after a groundbreaking semester,
they continue to steer both their school and community toward unity.
But the arrival of a new group of outsiders – mysterious werewolves – threatens to shake up
the newfound peace and causes a rift in Zed and Addison’s budding romance.
Addison, played by Meg Donnelly.
Zed, played by Milo Manheim.
Willa, played by Chandler Kinney.
Bucky, played by Trevor Tordjman.
Eliza, played by Kylee Russell.
Bree, played by Carla Jeffery.
The film explores themes of love triangle, musical, cheerleading, love, zombie.
The tone is emotional.